https://childrenswish.org/about/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Welcome to the www.childrenswish.org web site (the “Web Site”). Your privacy is important to us and Children’s Wish Foundation International (“CHILDREN’S WISH”) a nonprofit organization is committed to protecting your privacy and trust. This Privacy Policy applies to all portions of our Web Site. This Privacy Policy explains and describes how we collect, use and disclose information from you through your use of the Web Site and what we do with such information. By using this Web Site you agree and acknowledged that you have reviewed, and agree to, this Privacy Policy and its terms and conditions. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, or any of its subsequent modifications, do not use this Web Site. This site collects information such as the visitor’s domain name, site traffic patterns and server usage statistics. This information is used to improve the performance and content of our Web pages and to personalize content and layout of our pages for individual visitors.
CHILDREN’S WISH may at any time change this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy without advance notice and any modifications are effective when they are posted here. You should periodically visit this page to review the then-current Privacy Policy.
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, make a financial donation, respond to a survey or fill out a web form.
Personally identifiable information collected in these surveys will not be shared. Aggregate results may be shared for analysis by third parties. The aggregate data cannot be used to identify individuals.
Donations and Fundraising Events
When you donate to Children’s Wish Foundation International – a children’s charity organization, or register for a fundraising event, we ask you to voluntarily provide your name, address, telephone number, email address and credit card number so we can process your donation or event registration, send you a receipt or confirmation and communicate with you if necessary.
If you’d like, you can provide that information another way (by phone or US postal service). When you make a gift on our site, your information goes into our database and you may then be sent emails or mailings about other opportunities to support the Children’s Wish Foundation.
You can opt-out at any time by emailing wishes@childrenswish.org or address a letter to:
Children’s Wish Foundation International
8615 Roswell Road, Atlanta, GA 30350-7526
You may also opt out using any of the opt-out methods, such as check-box opt-outs, included in any fundraising solicitation by the Children’s Wish Foundation.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
To improve our website
(we continually strive to improve our website based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
To improve our donor, visitor and funder experience
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your requests and needs)
To process transactions
We do not collect and store your email address unless you choose to communicate with us in one of several ways:
You contact us directly via email.
You provide your email address to us via phone, mail, electronic form or paper sign-up sheet.
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent.
To administer a contest, survey or other site feature
To send periodic emails
The email address you provide for donation processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your donation, in addition to receiving occasional Foundation news, updates, related to the organization, its programs, etc.
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions within each email.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place a donation or enter, submit, or access your personal information.
We use a credit card processor for donations. These companies do not share or use personally identifiable information for secondary purposes.
Our server uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption to protect credit card and other information submitted via the forms on this site. SSL is the industry standard security protocol. All off-line information is securely stored and is accessible only by authorized staff.
Do we use cookies?
Yes, we use cookies to store visitors’ preferences, alert visitors to new areas of the site, customize Web page content based on visitor interests and record past activity in order to provide better service. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser, capture and remember certain information.
Most browsers will allow a user to accept or deny cookies.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or other’s rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Third-party personally identifiable information you provide for memorial or honor donations will not be shared.
Online Privacy Policy
This online privacy policy applies to information collected through our website as well as information collected offline.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification on our website.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:
Search for:
8615 Roswell Road,
Atlanta, GA 30350
pinterestlinkedintwitterfacebook
A Day to Remember Can Help a Child Forget | Phone: 1-800-323-WISH | Privacy Policy | Financial Information
www.childrenswish.org © 2015
Google Grant management is provided by Elevate Clicks,
a PPC management agency.
